<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<root>
	<element>
		<supplierindex>1</supplierindex>
		<name>AMResorts</name>
		<logoimage>amresorts_logo.png</logoimage>
		<amenities>Elegant accommodations with ocean view | Welcome cocktail and cool towel |Gourmet dining at our six restaurants|Full breakfast, lunch, dinner and snacks each day|24-hour room and concierge services|Complimentary mini bar refreshed daily|Unlimited premium drinks at two bars and lounges|Unlimited natural fruit juices and soft drinks|Day and nighttime activities and entertainment|Pool and beach concierge|3 pools including 2 infinity pools|Expansive, private beach|Golf Desk|Fitness center|All taxes and gratuities</amenities>
		<titlecopy>Discover AMResorts</titlecopy>
		<bodycopy>Each with its own charming design, Zoëtry Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts, Secrets, Breathless, Dreams, Now and Sunscape Resorts &amp; Spas will surely take your breath away. Specializing in luxury accommodations, guest rooms and suites are elegantly designed. The cuisine chefs specialize in gourmet dining and the world class spas make for a serene experience. The landscapes of these resorts make the ideal backdrop of your dream wedding or honeymoon so your time together will be in the perfect setting. 
 
AMResorts is the provider of sales, marketing and brand management services to six brands of exclusive resort properties in Mexico, Jamaica and the Dominican Republic: ultra luxurious Zoëtry Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts, adults-only Secrets Resorts &amp; Spas, sophisticated Breathless Resorts &amp; Spas, luxurious Dreams Resorts &amp; Spas, vibrant and contemporary Now Resorts &amp; Spas and fun-filled Sunscape Resorts &amp; Spas. Zoëtry Paraiso de la Bonita Riviera Maya and Secrets Marquis Los Cabos are members of Leading Hotels of the World.
Each with its own charming design, Zoëtry Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts, Secrets, Breathless, Dreams, Now and Sunscape Resorts &amp; Spas will surely take your breath away. Specializing in luxury accommodations, guest rooms and suites are elegantly designed. The cuisine chefs specialize in gourmet dining and the world class spas make for a serene experience. The landscapes of these resorts make the ideal backdrop of your dream wedding or honeymoon so your time together will be in the perfect setting. 
 
AMResorts is the provider of sales, marketing and brand management services to six brands of exclusive resort properties in Mexico, Jamaica and the Dominican Republic: ultra luxurious Zoëtry Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts, adults-only Secrets Resorts &amp; Spas, sophisticated Breathless Resorts &amp; Spas, luxurious Dreams Resorts &amp; Spas, vibrant and contemporary Now Resorts &amp; Spas and fun-filled Sunscape Resorts &amp; Spas. Zoëtry Paraiso de la Bonita Riviera Maya and Secrets Marquis Los Cabos are members of Leading Hotels of the World.
Each with its own charming design, Zoëtry Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts, Secrets, Breathless, Dreams, Now and Sunscape Resorts &amp; Spas will surely take your breath away. Specializing in luxury accommodations, guest rooms and suites are elegantly designed. The cuisine chefs specialize in gourmet dining and the world class spas make for a serene experience. The landscapes of these resorts make the ideal backdrop of your dream wedding or honeymoon so your time together will be in the perfect setting. 
 
AMResorts is the provider of sales, marketing and brand management services to six brands of exclusive resort properties in Mexico, Jamaica and the Dominican Republic: ultra luxurious Zoëtry Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts, adults-only Secrets Resorts &amp; Spas, sophisticated Breathless Resorts &amp; Spas, luxurious Dreams Resorts &amp; Spas, vibrant and contemporary Now Resorts &amp; Spas and fun-filled Sunscape Resorts &amp; Spas. Zoëtry Paraiso de la Bonita Riviera Maya and Secrets Marquis Los Cabos are members of Leading Hotels of the World.
Each with its own charming design, Zoëtry Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts, Secrets, Breathless, Dreams, Now and Sunscape Resorts &amp; Spas will surely take your breath away. Specializing in luxury accommodations, guest rooms and suites are elegantly designed. The cuisine chefs specialize in gourmet dining and the world class spas make for a serene experience. The landscapes of these resorts make the ideal backdrop of your dream wedding or honeymoon so your time together will be in the perfect setting. 
 
AMResorts is the provider of sales, marketing and brand management services to six brands of exclusive resort properties in Mexico, Jamaica and the Dominican Republic: ultra luxurious Zoëtry Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts, adults-only Secrets Resorts &amp; Spas, sophisticated Breathless Resorts &amp; Spas, luxurious Dreams Resorts &amp; Spas, vibrant and contemporary Now Resorts &amp; Spas and fun-filled Sunscape Resorts &amp; Spas. Zoëtry Paraiso de la Bonita Riviera Maya and Secrets Marquis Los Cabos are members of Leading Hotels of the World.


AMResorts is the provider of sales, marketing and brand management services to five brands of exclusive resort properties in Mexico, Jamaica and the Dominican Republic: ultra luxurious Zoëtry® Wellness &amp; Spa Resorts; adults-only Secrets® Resorts &amp; Spas; luxurious Dreams® Resorts &amp; Spas; vibrant and contemporary Now® Resorts &amp; Spas;  fun-filled Sunscape® Resorts &amp; Spas and the seductive and chic Breathless Resorts &amp; Spas. Zoëtry Paraiso de la Bonita Riviera Maya and Secrets Marquis Los Cabos are members of Leading Hotels of the World.</bodycopy>
		<teasercopy>AMResorts teaser copy.</teasercopy>
	</element>
	<element>
		<supplierindex>2</supplierindex>
		<name>All-Inclusive Hard Rock Hotels</name>
		<logoimage>hardrock_logo.png</logoimage>
		<amenities>Luxurious accommodations|Fine dining|Delicious snacks|Top shelf drinks|24-Hour room service|Sensational Daily &amp; Nightly Entertainment|Wireless Internet &amp; Unlimited phone calls within the Dominican Republic and to the Continental US and Canada|Included internet use (30 minutes) in the business center, per room/per stay|Taxes &amp; Gratuities</amenities>
		<titlecopy>Celebrate your love at a killer all-inclusive HardRock resort</titlecopy>
		<bodycopy>The new all inclusive Hard Rock Hotels located in Mexico and Dominican Republic offer a one-of-a-kind, all day, all night, all-inclusive vacation experience. Resorts include: Hard Rock Hotel &amp; Casino Punta Cana in the Dominican Republic (the world’s first all-inclusive Hard Rock Hotel and AAA Four Diamond resort) and three Mexico properties in Cancun, Vallarta and Riviera Maya.

Whether you’re rocking out at one of the nightly concerts, indulging in the awesome collection of water sports or being pampered in excess, Hard Rock Hotels make your rock star fantasies a reality. And when you’re through turning your notches all the way up, turn them down at Hard Rock’s world-renowned Rock Spa® or by one of the alluring pools with a view of the tropics. Celebrate your big day and lavish in luxury.</bodycopy>
		<teasercopy></teasercopy>
	</element>
	<element>
		<supplierindex>3</supplierindex>
		<name>Palace Resorts and Le Blanc Spa Resort</name>
		<logoimage>palace_leblanc_logo.png</logoimage>
		<amenities>Luxurious Accommodations | Fine Dining | Delicious Snacks | Top Shelf Drinks |24 Hour Room Service | Non-Motorized Water Sports at select locations | Sensational Daily &amp; Nightly Entertainment | CHI Professional Blow Dryer and Hair Iron |Wireless Internet | Unlimited Phone Calls within Mexico and to the Continental US and Canada. Some restrictions apply. | Included Internet Use (30 minutes) in the business center, per room/per stay | Taxes &amp; Gratuities | Use of the facilities of all IHR Properties in Cancun, Riviera Maya, Playa del Carmen, Cozumel, and Isla Mujeres. IHR guests do not share exchange privileges at Le Blanc Spa Resort (Day pass purchase is required). | Luxury Accommodations| Haute Cuisine | Delectable Snacks | Premium Drinks (Brand name Spirits &amp; Wine) |Personalized Service with nearly on Staff per Guest |Upscale Room Amenities | 24 Hour Room Service | Non-motorized Water sports at Wet n’ Wild | Dazzling Entertainment | Wireless Internet  |Unlimited Phone Calls within Mexico and the Continental US and Canada- Some restrictions apply |Included Internet use (30 minutes per room, per stay, in the business center |Taxes and Gratuities | Use of the facilities of all IHR properties in Cancun, Riviera Maya, Cozumel, and Isla Mujeres |Access to the hydrotherapy area* in the spa at Le Blanc Spa Resort- Some restrictions apply. Service is subject to space and availability. Prior reservations are required upon check-in. Spa treatments and massages are not included. Applicable to all room categories.</amenities>
		<titlecopy>Pleasure in every sense at Le Blanc Spa Resort | Live in awe at Palace Resorts</titlecopy>
		<bodycopy>Palace Resorts offer signature amenities and unparalleled service that will leave you in awe of the exceptional all-inclusive vacation experience provided. The oceanfront accommodations feature spacious family rooms and suites with double Whirlpool tubs, luxurious amenities including 24-hour room service, fine dining, championship golf courses and world-class spas (both available at an additional cost). The new Awe-inclusive concept enhances Palace's already superb amenities with features such as premium spirits, and the Family Connections program, which includes guaranteed connecting suites and Nanny service. Whether day or night, exceptional celebrity entertainment will make for an experience to remember with artists like Ricky Martin! Whatever your needs, let Palace Resorts help you relax and rejuvenate. 

The adults only Le Blanc Spa Resort is located in the heart of the Hotel Zone facing a spectacular and white sandy beach. Known for its impeccable personalized service, with a butler on every floor and with nearly one staff per guest, this resort allows each guest to feel pampered. Indulge in every way possible, whether at the spa (services available at additional charge), at one of the five delicious restaurants or poolside with a cool beverage. The signature spa provides every guest with a rejuvenating experience for the mind, body and soul. For the ideal newlywed experience, have your wedding or honeymoon (packages available at additional cost) at the AAA five-diamond award winning, Le Blanc Spa Resort, where the world is your own. No children. No distractions. No interruptions. All of this and more awaits you at Le Blanc Spa Resort. Pleasure in every sense.</bodycopy>
		<teasercopy></teasercopy>
	</element>
	<element>
		<supplierindex>4</supplierindex>
		<name>RIU Hotels &amp; Resorts</name>
		<logoimage>riu_logo.png</logoimage>
		<amenities>All meals and snacks-Breakfast-Full American breakfast buffet and on the spot cooking stations-Continental breakfast/snacks|Lunch-Hot and cold buffet and on the spot cooking stations -Pizzas, pasta, salads and assorted desserts | Dinner-Buffets and dishes prepared on the spot-Special evenings: theme buffet twice a week | Optional dining (reservations required in advance)-Grill and steakhouse (à la carte)-"Maria Margarita" Mexican restaurant (à la carte; buffet starters and dessert)-"Shangri-la" Asian restaurant (buffet)|Formal dress is required for dinner (main restaurant: T Shirts with sleeves for gentlemen; theme restaurants: long trousers and T Shirts with sleeves for gentlemen)|Snacks 24 hours a day-Beverages-Local and imported beverages served 24 hours a day-Regularly restocked mini-bar and liquor dispenser | In-room safe | Sports and activities-2 tennis courts-Gym, sauna, steam bath and Jacuzzi-Table tennis, beach volleyball, aerobics, airgun shooting-Windsurfing, catamaran, kayaking, body boarding and snorkeling equipment-1 introductory scuba diving lesson in the pool | Entertainment-Daytime entertainment programme for children ages 4 to 7 and ages 8 to 12 at RiuLand (daily) -Daytime entertainment programme for adults (daily)-Riu evening programme, shows or live music (daily)|All accommodations, taxes and gratuities</amenities>
		<titlecopy>Experience Riu Hotels &amp; Resorts</titlecopy>
		<bodycopy>These hotels are located just footsteps from the beach and boast impeccable swimming pools, tennis courts and restaurants that make for both exciting days and nights. With all-inclusive service, entertainment, sports and dining, and complimentary Wi-Fi in the lobby area (and in the guestrooms at Palace properties), your experiences will keep you coming back to RIU Hotels &amp; Resorts for more. Delight in the rich flavors and colors of Riu’s rich cuisine. And if you’re looking to relax, soak in the sun and cool ocean breeze while you sit under the palm trees on of Riu’s white sand beaches. Or tap into your adventurous side with activities like windsurfing and body boarding.</bodycopy>
		<teasercopy></teasercopy>
	</element>
	<element>
		<supplierindex>5</supplierindex>
		<name>Bahia Principe Hotels &amp; Resorts</name>
		<logoimage>bahia_logo.png</logoimage>
		<amenities>Towel service in the main pool|International entertainment program for adults|Organized games and activities|Mini-bar with water, soft drinks and beer|Replenishment once a day, Sports: 1 hour free-Windsurfing, Catamaran, Kayaks, Boogie boards, Snorkeling |Sports upon request: Volleyball|Try the scuba diving equipment in the pool, Daily tennis, Gym, Aerobics|Transportation to Pueblo Príncipe|All local taxes and tips|3 Dinners in à la carte Restaurants per week of stay and with previous booking</amenities>
		<titlecopy>Exceed your expectations at Bahia Principe Hotels &amp; Resorts</titlecopy>
		<bodycopy>Bahia Principe Hotels &amp; Resorts offers one of the world’s most breathtaking beachfront settings, spacious accommodations, an unparalleled array of restaurants, bars, daily activities, sports entertainment, live shows...and more all included in the 24-hour all inclusive plan!

Take a dip and enjoy snorkeling off of the coast of one of Bahia Principe’s beautiful beaches or get in a game of beach volleyball. Once you’ve finished rediscovering your adventurous side, indulge in the colorful and mouth watering dishes, elegantly prepared by one of the talented chefs. Celebrate your wedding or honeymoon and relax and be pampered at Bahia Principe Hotels &amp; Resorts.</bodycopy>
		<teasercopy></teasercopy>
	</element>
	<element>
		<supplierindex>6</supplierindex>
		<name>IBEROSTAR Hotels &amp; Resorts</name>
		<logoimage>iberostar_logo.png</logoimage>
		<amenities>Breakfast, lunch, and dinner|National and international beverages in the hotel's bars,|Entertainment program |Sports: target shooting, basketball, beach volleyball, dance lessons, darts, soccer, water aerobics, ping pong, tennis, water polo|and access to hotel fitness center.</amenities>
		<titlecopy>Create memories that will last a lifetime at IBEROSTAR Hotels&amp; Resorts</titlecopy>
		<bodycopy>IBEROSTAR Hotels &amp; Resorts are in the ideal locations to set up your dream getaway. Stay at one of their beachfront resorts and let the sun be your alarm clock and let the moon tuck you in. Enjoy any of the IBEROSTAR properties to receive 5-star treatment and be pampered in luxurious all-inclusive accommodations. Food lovers, golfers, adventurous and beach lovers alike can enjoy these resorts’ entertainment options, spa facilities and pools. For the perfect wedding or honeymoon, let IBEROSTAR meet your needs.</bodycopy>
		<teasercopy></teasercopy>
	</element>
</root>
